import 'package:flutter/material.dart';

List<Map> QBank = [
  {
    'id': 1,
    'bgcolor': Colors.red,
    'question': "1. How many colors are there on the Indian Flag?",
    'ans': 'o_c',
    'o_a': 'A. 4',
    'o_b': 'B. 5',
    'o_c': 'C. 3',
    'o_d': 'D. 2',
  },
  {
    'id': 2,
    'bgcolor': Colors.amber,
    'question': "2. How many hours are there in a day?",
    'ans': 'o_d',
    'o_a': 'A. 20',
    'o_b': 'B. 12',
    'o_c': 'C. 64',
    'o_d': 'D. 24',
  },
  {
    'id': 3,
    'bgcolor': Colors.blue,
    'question': "3. Who is current the PM of india?",
    'ans': 'o_a',
    'o_a': 'A. Narendra Modi',
    'o_b': 'B. Amit Shah',
    'o_c': 'C. Rahul Gandhi',
    'o_d': 'D. Yogi Adityanath',
  },
  {
    'id': 4,
    'bgcolor': Colors.lightBlue,
    'question': "4. National animal of india?",
    'ans': 'o_c',
    'o_a': 'A. Cow',
    'o_b': 'B. Dog',
    'o_c': 'C. Tiger',
    'o_d': 'D. Bull',
  },
  {
    'id': 5,
    'bgcolor': Colors.lime,
    'question': "5. Container is single child or multi child..?",
    'ans': 'o_a',
    'o_a': 'A. Single',
    'o_b': 'B. Multi',
    'o_c': 'C. Both a&b',
    'o_d': 'D. All of above',
  },
  {
    'id': 6,
    'bgcolor': Colors.orange,
    'question': "6. Who built the Taj Mahal..?",
    'ans': 'o_b',
    'o_a': 'A. Akbar',
    'o_b': 'B. Shahjahan',
    'o_c': 'C. Aurang jeb',
    'o_d': 'D. None',
  },
  {
    'id': 7,
    'bgcolor': Colors.pink,
    'question': "7. What is the capital of india?",
    'ans': 'o_b',
    'o_a': 'A. Gujrat',
    'o_b': 'B. Delhi',
    'o_c': 'C. Surat',
    'o_d': 'D. Goa',
  },
  {
    'id': 8,
    'bgcolor': Colors.purple,
    'question': "8. On which date did india become independent ?",
    'ans': 'o_a',
    'o_a': 'A. August 15',
    'o_b': 'B. 1 may',
    'o_c': 'C. 10 april',
    'o_d': 'D. 26 january',
  },
  {
    'id': 9,
    'bgcolor': Colors.teal,
    'question': "9. How many days are there in a week ?",
    'ans': 'o_b',
    'o_a': 'A. 8',
    'o_b': 'B. 7',
    'o_c': 'C. 10',
    'o_d': 'D. 30',
  },
  {
    'id': 10,
    'bgcolor': Colors.tealAccent,
    'question': "10. whis is national game of india?",
    'ans': 'o_a',
    'o_a': 'A. Hocky',
    'o_b': 'B. Football',
    'o_c': 'C. Wallyball',
    'o_d': 'D. Kabadi',
  },
];
